[{"answer": "It's just the results.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What makes you say that?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, Putin is playing games.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Pretty tough thumping piece here, what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well, I -- first his leadership has absolutely failed in this regard and we are not in the position of strength right now, I mean to suggest the President speech last night was anything but another capitulation, another, you know, obvious delaying tactic to something he doesn't want to do and he's trying to find a reason not to do it has created Putin the peace maker.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "A stinging attack on the President personally to the leadership he's shown over this, did you agree with it?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Yes, I believe there is incontrovertible evidence.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Is there incontrovertible evidence to the satisfaction of impartial observers that says it was definitely Assad that ordered this chemical attack?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well look ...", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "We don't know who these rebels are really, do we?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing to say is I think the story is over, because Putin now wears this and we're not going to attack.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "And what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think the last individual in the broader world community that the United States, our President, and Republicans and Democrats should take advice from is Vladimir Putin.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Does he have a point?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, it diminishes whatever credibility you may have had or may have build up over the past five years and Lincoln argue that we -- if he hasn't been as assertive on certain occasions as some of us wish he had been.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Where does that leave your authority?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "In a sense, yes.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Would you ever hold a lot of people now who literally just sit there, trying to work out any possible way that an attack can come?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "New York is very resilient.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What is your sense about the spirit of New Yorkers that you built up in all your time working in the police department here?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Oh, undoubtedly no question about it and we've invested a lot, the federal government has invested a lot, you know, we've been able to in some way shape perform with the federal government to prevent these 16 attacks.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "A final question, Commissioner, did you believe that New York is a safer city?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "We raised $12 million today for about a 100 charities around the world.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "I was at your offices today; you have this extraordinary charity day where all the trading profits around the world to Cantor Fitzgerald go to charity, how much do you raised?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we -- usually when someone is going to make a documentary about you we'd sit around, we discussed it aside, is this a good idea or not.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "A new documentary, \"Out of the Clear Blue Sky\" tells that the story from start to finish you've seen this film now, I take, what did you make of it?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I guess it's two-fold.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "So, what is your reaction to the critics who'd come out chopping your record?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Did you have anybody helped you touch a boat to get a rest or anything of that nature?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Piers, it never happened, you know, we've got careful loggers out there evidently a doctor said -- Dr. Derek Covington with University of Miami said she had terrible stomach issues because of taking in those saltwater.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "They say you didn't eat or drink for nearly seven hours and 53 right in the middle of it which should be impossible, what's the truth?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Listen, listen these are the most dangerous jellyfish in the world, they're fatal.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "How do you plead?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, Piers to harken and back to 9/11 as we come on the anniversary of hurricane Sandy in New York City, we have built a pool, we're going to put it in Herald Square right in the middle of New York City on the anniversary of the storm.", "docId": "130911pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Any big new plans in the pipeline?", "qSentId": 458}]